<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">FragmentFit</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_base">BaseActivity</string>
    
    <string-array name="exercisesChestUp">
        <item><b>BENCH PRESS:</b> 3 sets, 8 reps with maximum weight</item>
        <item>BARBELL BENCH PRESS: 3 sets, 8 reps with maximum weight</item>
        <item>FLY: 3 sets, 8 reps with maximum weight</item>
        <item>BUTTERFLY: 3 sets, 8 reps with maximum weight</item>
        <item>PUSHUPS: 4 sets, until failure. Try to do atleast 20 per set</item>
        <item>CABLE ROWS: 3 sets, 8 reps with maximum weight</item>
        <item>WIDE GRIP PULLUPS: 3 sets until failure</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exercisesChestDown">
        <item><b>BENCH PRESS:</b> 5 sets with 15-20 reps each set or until failure</item>
        <item>BARBELL BENCH PRESS: 5 sets, 15-20 reps with low weight</item>
        <item>FLY: 5 sets, reps with low weight, until failure</item>
        <item>BUTTERFLY: 5 sets, atleast 15 reps with low weight</item>
        <item>PUSHUPS: until failure, they increase the muscle strenght</item>
        <item>CABLE ROWS: 5 sets, 15 to 20 reps with minimum weight</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exercisesWaist">
        <item>SIDE PLANK: 3 sets, each about 30-35 seconds</item>
        <item>LEG RAISES: 10 minute workout raising legs for 20seconds and drop for 10 seconds, repeat</item>
        <item>SITUPS: 5 sets with 25 reps or more</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exercisesHipsUp">
        <item>SQUATS: 3 sets, 8 reps with maximum weight</item>
        <item>STEPPER: atleast 10-15 minute workout</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exercisesHipsDown">
        <item>SQUATS: 5 sets, 15 to 20 reps with minimum weight</item>
        <item>STEPPER: atleast 30-45 minute workout</item>
        <item>BYCICLE: atleast 45 to 60 minute workout</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- stringi samo za exercises -->

    <string-array name="Chest">
        <item>Lie supine on bench. Dismount barbell from 
		rack over upper chest using wide oblique overhand grip.
		Lower weight to mid-chest.
		Press bar upward until arms are extended. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Position yourself on a free standing flat bench,
		flat on your back. Have your spotter hand you each 
		dumbbell. When you begin this movement, you want your
		arms to be stretched out wide to your sides with your
		elbows slightly bent and your palms facing inward, 
		toward one another.At the peak of the movement,
		really squeeze your pecs together for a one-count. 
		When returning to the start position, 
		be sure to lower the dumbbells
		in a slow and controlled fashion. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Sit down on bench with dumbbells resting on lower thigh.
		Kick weights to shoulder and lie back. 
		Position dumbbells to sides of chest with bent 
		arm under each dumbbell.Press dumbbells up with 
		elbows to sides until arms are extended. 
		Lower weight to sides of upper chest until slight 
		stretch is felt in chest or shoulder. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Position yourself on a free standing flat bench,
		flat on your back. Have your spotter hand you each 
		dumbbell. When you begin this movement, you want your
		arms to be stretched out wide to your sides with your
		elbows slightly bent and your palms facing inward, 
		toward one another.At the peak of the movement,
		really squeeze your pecs together for a one-count. 
		When returning to the start position, 
		be sure to lower the dumbbells
		in a slow and controlled fashion. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Set up the cable machine for crossovers 
		by adjusting the pulleys to the highest point 
		possible on both sides and attaching single 
		grip handles.Set your desired weight on the 
		weight stacks and grasp each handle with your 
		palms facing down.Take a step forward.
		Bend your arms slightly at the elbows. 
		Keep your chest up and eyes facing forwards. 
		This is the starting position for the exercise.
		Rotating at the shoulders only and moving your 
		arms in a circular motion, slowly bring the 
		handles together out in front of your body 
		at mid-chest height. Squeeze your chest as 
		you bring the handles together.
		Slowly lower the weight back to the starting 
		position and repeat.</item>
        <item>Lie prone on floor with hands slightly wider
		than shoulder width. Raise body up off floor 
		by extend arms with body straight.	
		Keeping body straight, lower body to floor by 
		bending arms. Push body up until arms are extended. 
		Repeat.  </item>
        <item>Sit on seat and grasp stirrups to each side. 
		Position elbows out to sides, slightly lower 
		than shoulder height. Position hands slightly 
		narrower than elbow width in front of upper arms.
		Push stirrups out straight until arms are straight 
		and parallel to one another. Return stirrups to 
		original position, until slight stretch is felt in 
		shoulders or chest. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Sit in machine with back on pad. If available, 
		push foot lever until padded lever moves forward. 
		Place forearms on padded lever. Position upper 
		arms approximately parallel. Release foot lever.
		Push levers together. Return until chest muscles 
		are stretched. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Lie supine on incline/decline bench. 
		Dismount barbell from rack over upper chest 
		using wide oblique overhand grip.
		Lower weight to upper chest. Press bar until 
		arms are extended. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Lie upper back perpendicular on bench. 
		Flex hips slightly. Grasp one dumbbell from 
		behind or from side with both hands under inner 
		plate of dumbbell. Position dumbbell over chest 
		with elbows slightly bent. Keeping elbows slightly 
		bent throughout movement, lower dumbbell over and 
		beyond head until upper arms are in-line with torso. 
		Pull dumbbell up and over chest. Repeat.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Shoulder">
        <item>Grasp dumbbells in front of thighs with 
	elbows slightly bent. Bend over slightly 
	with hips and knees bent slightly.
	Raise upper arms to sides until elbows 
	are shoulder height. Maintain elbows 
	height above or equal to wrists. Lower and repeat.</item>
        <item>	Stand holding dumbbells to sides.
	Elevate shoulders as high as possible.
	Lower and repeat.</item>
        <item>Grasp barbell with slightly wider than shoulder 
	width overhand grip from rack. Position bar near 
	upper chest. Press bar upward until arms are 
	extended overhead. Return to upper chest and repeat.</item>
        <item>	Stand with two dumbbells position in front 
	of shoulders, palms facing body and elbows under wrists.
	Initiate movement by bringing elbows out to sides. 
	Continue to raise elbows outward while pressing 
	dumbbells overhead until arms are straight. 
	Lower to front of shoulders in opposite pattern and repeat.</item>
        <item>Grasp barbell from rack or clean barbell 
	from floor with overhand grip, slightly 
	wider than shoulder width. Position bar 
	in front of neck. Press bar upward until
	 arms are extended overhead. Lower to front 
	of neck and repeat.</item>
        <item>Adjust the seat height so that the handles are 
	at shoulder height.
	Select an appropriate weight for the exercise.
	Take hold of the handles with both hands, 
	take a deep breath in and whilst exhaling extend 
	the arms upwards. Pause briefly at the top of the 
	movement and lower back to the start position whilst inhaling.
	Repeat for the desired number of repetitions.</item>
        <item>Grasp bar with shoulder width or slightly narrower 
	overhand grip. Pull bar to neck with elbows leading. 
	Allow wrists to flex as bar rises. Lower and repeat
</item>
        <item>Grasp plate in both hands. Position plate 
	in front of upper legs with elbows straight or 
	slightly bent. Raise plate forward and upward 
	with until upper arms are above horizontal. Lower and repeat.</item>
        <item>Grasp dumbbells to each side. Bend knees and bend over through hips 
	with back flat close to horizontal. Position elbows with slight bend
	and palms facing together. Raise upper arms to sides until elbows 
	are shoulder height. Maintain upper arms perpendicular to torso 
	and fixed elbow position (10° to 30° angle) throughout exercise. 
	Maintain height of elbows above wrists by raising "pinkie finger" side up. 
	Lower and repeat.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Back">
        <item>With feet flat beneath bar, squat down and grasp bar with 
	shoulder width or slightly wider over hand or mixed grip.
	Lift bar by extending hips and knees to full extension. 
	Pull shoulders back at top of lift if rounded. Return and repeat.</item>
        <item>Step up and grasp bar with overhand wide grip.
	Pull body up until chin is above bar. Lower body 
	until arms and shoulders are fully extended. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Your move Holding dumbbells, bend at your knees and hips, 
	and lower your torso until it’s parallel to the floor. 
	Let the weights hang down. Then pull your shoulders back and 
	hold for a second. Next, lift the weights to the sides of your 
	torso by squeezing your shoulder blades towards your spine. 
	Lower and repeat.</item>
        <item>Your move Set a barbell at knee level in a squat rack 
	and grab it with an overhand grip, hands wider than your legs. 
	Then stand up, pushing your hips forward. Begin with no weight 
	until it feels natural. When this exercise becomes easy, 
	lift the barbell from the floor.</item>
        <item>Sit slightly forward on seat or bench and grasp cable attachment. 
	Place feet on vertical platform. Slide hips back positioning knees with slight bend.
	Pull cable attachment to waist while straightening lower back. Pull shoulders 
	back and push chest forward while arching back. Return until arms are extended, 
	shoulders are stretched forward, and lower back is flexed forward. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Kneel over side of bench by placing knee and hand of supporting arm on bench. 
	Position foot of opposite leg slightly back to side. Grasp dumbbell from floor.
	Pull dumbbell to up to side until it makes contact with ribs or until 
	upper arm is just beyond horizontal. Return until arm is extended and shoulder 
	is stretched downward. Repeat and continue with opposite arm.</item>
        <item>Use light-medium dumbbells and begin in a seated position, bent over with 
	arms hanging down and weights under the knees.
	Try not to collapse on the legs but, instead, keep the back straight and the abs engaged.
	Lift the arms out to the sides, up to shoulder level, squeezing shoulder blades together.
	Keep the elbows slightly bent and only lift to shoulders.</item>
        <item>Lie facedown, legs together and extended straight, arms bent with hands behind neck, head and neck in a neutral position. 
	EXHALE: Lift the upper body (chest, shoulders) off of the ground, "crunching" towards the hips. 
	Hold for 1-2 counts at highest position. 
	INHALE: Slowly lower with control to start to complete one rep.</item>
        <item>Bend knees slightly and bend over bar with back straight. 
	Grasp bar with wide overhand grip.
	Pull bar to upper waist. Return until arms are 
	extended and shoulders are stretched downward. Repeat.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Abs">
        <item>Sit on apparatus with lower leg secured under padded bar. 
	Hold weight to front of chest or behind neck or use no weight.
	Lower body back until hips are almost extended. 
	Raise body by flexing hips until torso is upright. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Lie face up on your mat and place your hands behind your head, lightly supporting it with your fingers.
	Bring the knees in to the chest and lift the shoulder blades off the floor without pulling on the neck.
	Rotate to the left, bringing the right elbow towards the left knee as you straighten the other leg.
	Switch sides, bringing the left elbow towards the right knee.</item>
        <item>Stand on the chair and grip handholds to stabilize your upper body.
	Press your back against the pad and contract the abs to raise the legs and lift knees towards your chest.
	Do not arch the back or swing the legs up.</item>
        <item>Lie on the ball, positioning it under the lower back.
	Cross your arms over the chest or place them behind your head.
	Contract your abs to lift your torso off the ball, pulling the bottom of your ribcage down toward your hips.
	As you curl up, keep the ball stable.</item>
        <item>Lie on the floor and extend the legs straight up with knees crossed.
	Place your hands behind the head for support, but avoid pulling on the neck.
	Contract the abs to lift the shoulder blades off the floor, as though reaching your chest towards your feet.
	Keep the legs in a fixed position and imagine bringing your belly button towards your spine at the top of the movement.</item>
        <item>Lie face down on mat resting on the forearms, palms flat on the floor.
	Push off the floor, raising up onto toes and resting on the elbows.
	Keep your back flat, in a straight line from head to heels.</item>
        <item>Grasp dumbbell with arm straight to side.
	Bend waist to opposite side of dumbbell until slight stretch is felt. 
	Lower to opposite side same distance and repeat. Continue with opposite side.</item>
        <item>Start with the wheel at your feet, with your arms and legs straight.
	Now roll the wheel out until you are laid out as far as you can go, 
	but still under control. Then pull everything back until your hands 
	and feet come back together.</item>
        <item>Grasp and hang from high bar with slightly wider than shoulder width overhand grip.
	Raise legs by flexing hips and knees until hips are completely flexed or 
	knees are well above hips. Return until hips and knees are extended downward. Repeat.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Arms">
        <item>Grasp bar with shoulder width under hand grip.
	With elbows to side, raise bar until forearms are vertical. 
	Lower until arms are fully extended. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Sit on bench. Grasp dumbbell between feet. Place back of upper 
	arm to inner thigh. Lean into leg to raise elbow slightly.
	Raise dumbbell to front of shoulder. Lower dumbbell until arm is 
	fully extended. Repeat. Continue with opposite arm.</item>
        <item>Position two dumbbells to sides, palms facing in, arms straight.	
	With elbows to sides, raise one dumbbell until forearm is vertical and 
	thumb faces shoulder. Lower to original position and repeat with alternative arm.</item>
        <item>Grab the chinup bar with an underhand grip but with your hands 6 to 8 inches apart, not shoulder-width.
	When you place your hands closer together, your biceps become even more involved in the exercise. 
	This makes the exercise easier than the classic chinup.
	Keeping your arms completely straight and crossing your ankles behind you, hang at arms length.
	You should return to this position—known as a dead hang—each time you lower your body back down.</item>
        <item>Kneel over bench with arm supporting body. Grasp dumbbell. Position upper arm parallel to floor.
	Extend arm until it is straight. Return and repeat. Continue with opposite arm.</item>
        <item>Mount shoulder width dip bar, arms straight with shoulders above hands. Keep hips straight.
	Lower body until slight stretch is felt in shoulders. Push body up until arms are straight. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Lie on bench with narrow overhand grip on barbell. Position barbell over shoulders with arms extended.
	Lower bar to forehead by bending elbows. Extend arms and repeat.</item>
        <item>Begin the move by positioning the hands on the mat directly under the chest with the fingers spread 
	and the thumbs and forefingers touching, making a triangle shape.
	Straighten the legs into a plank position (harder) or keep the knees on the floor for an easier version.
	Make sure the back is flat and the abs are engaged as you bend the elbows, lowering until your chin or 
	chest touches the mat. If you cannot go that low, go as low as you can and work to build enough strength to lower all the way down over time.
	At the bottom of the movement, your elbows will naturally flare out to the side.</item>
        <item>Stand in front of a cable machine, holding onto the bar with the elbows bent to about 90 degrees.
	Keeping the elbows stationary, push the bar down, contracting the triceps as you extend the arms.Repeat.</item>
        <item>Position one dumbbell overhead with both hands under inner plate (heart shaped grip).
	With elbows overhead, lower forearm behind upper arm by flexing elbows. 
	Flex wrists at bottom to avoid hitting dumbbell on back of neck. 
	Raise dumbbell overhead by extending elbows while hyperextending wrists. Return and repeat.</item>
        <item>Lie on bench and grasp barbell from rack with shoulder width grip.
	Lower weight to chest with elbows close to body. 
	Push barbell back up until arms are straight. Repeat.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Legs">
        <item>From rack with barbell at upper chest height, position bar high 
	on back of shoulders and grasp barbell to sides. Dismount bar from 
	rack and stand with shoulder width stance.
	Bend knees forward while allowing hips to bend back behind, 
	keeping back straight and knees pointed same direction as feet. 
	Descend until thighs are just past parallel to floor. 
	Extend knees and hips until legs are straight. Return and repeat.</item>
        <item>Stand with dumbbells grasped to sides.
	Lunge forward with first leg. Land on heel then forefoot. 
	Lower body by flexing knee and hip of front leg until knee of 
	rear leg is almost in contact with floor. Return to original standing 
	position by forcibly extending hip and knee of forward leg. 
	Repeat by alternating lunge with opposite leg.</item>
        <item>Sit on apparatus with back against padded back support. 
	Place back of lower leg on top of padded lever. Secure 
	lap pad against thigh just above knees. Grasp handles on lap support.
	Pull lever to back of thighs by flexing knees. 
	Return lever until knees are straight. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Sit on apparatus with back against padded back support. Place front of lower legs under padded lever. 
	Position knee articulation at same axis as lever fulcrum. Grasp handles to sides for support.
	Move lever forward and upward by extending knees until leg are straight. 
	Return lever to original position by bending knees. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Sit on machine with back on padded support. Place feet on platform. 
	Extend hips and knees. Release dock lever and grasp handles to sides.
	Lower sled by flexing hips and knees until knees are just short of complete flexion. 
	Return by extending knees and hips. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Stand in front of a secured box or platform.
	Jump onto box and immediately back down to same position. Immediately repeat.</item>
        <item>Set barbell on power rack upper chest height with calf block under barbell. 
	Position back of shoulders under barbell with both hands to sides. 
	Position toes and balls of feet on calf block with arches and heels extending off. 
	Lean barbell against rack and raise from supports by extending knees and hips. 
	Support barbell against verticals with both hands to sides.
	Raise heels by extending ankles as high as possible. Lower heels by bending ankles until calves are stretched. Repeat.</item>
        <item>Sit in machine with legs inside of side pads. If available, 
	place heels on foot bars. Release and pull lever brace to position legs together. 
	Engage lever into locked position. Lie back and grasp bars to sides.
	Move legs appart as far as possible. Return and repeat.</item>
        <item>Position barbell on back of shoulders and grasp barbell to sides. 
	Stand with feet far apart; one foot forward and other foot behind.
	Squat down by flexing knee and hip of front leg. 
	Allow heel of rear foot to rise up while knee of rear leg 
	bends slightly until it almost makes contact with floor. 
	Return to original standing position by extending hip and knee of forward leg. 
	Repeat. Continue with opposite leg.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="muscles">
        <item>CHEST</item>
        <item>SHOULDERS</item>
        <item>BACK</item>
        <item>ABS</item>
        <item>ARMS</item>
        <item>LEGS</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="chest_name_exercises">
        <item>Bench press </item>
        <item>Flat flyes </item>
        <item>Dumbbell press</item>
        <item>Dumbbell flyes </item>
        <item>Cable crossovers </item>
        <item>Pushups</item>
        <item>Cable press </item>
        <item>Pec deck</item>
        <item>Incline/decline barbell press</item>
        <item>Dumbbell pullover</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="shoulders_name_exercises">
        <item>Lateral raise</item>
        <item>Shrugs</item>
        <item>Overhead</item>
        <item>Arnold press</item>
        <item>Military press</item>
        <item>Shoulder press machine</item>
        <item>Barbell upright row</item>
        <item>Front plate raises</item>
        <item>Dumbell rear delt fly </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="back_name_exercises">
        <item>Deadlift</item>
        <item>Pull ups</item>
        <item>Big row</item>
        <item>Rack pack</item>
        <item>Seated cable row</item>
        <item>One arm dumbbell rows</item>
        <item>Reverse fly</item>
        <item>Back extensions</item>
        <item>Barbell rows</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="abs_name_exercises">
        <item>Decline weighted situps</item>
        <item>Bicycle excercise</item>
        <item>Captains chair leg raises</item>
        <item>Excercise ball crunch</item>
        <item>Vertical leg crunch</item>
        <item>Plank on elbows and toes</item>
        <item>Dumbell side bends</item>
        <item>Ab roller</item>
        <item>Hanging leg raises</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="arms_name_exercises">
        <item>Dumbell/barbell curls</item>
        <item>Concentration curls</item>
        <item>Hammer curls</item>
        <item>Close-grip chinup</item>
        <item>Triceps kickback</item>
        <item>Dibs</item>
        <item>Skull crushers</item>
        <item>Triangle pushup</item>
        <item>Bar pushdowns</item>
        <item>Triceps extension</item>
        <item>Close grip bench press</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="legs_name_exercises">
        <item>Squats </item>
        <item>Five way lunges</item>
        <item>Leg curl</item>
        <item>Leg extension</item>
        <item>Leg press machine</item>
        <item>Box jumps </item>
        <item>Dumbbell/machine calf raises</item>
        <item>Hip abduction machine</item>
        <item>Split squat</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
